[classical music playing]
[Jerry] This is a 1970
Mercedes Benz 280 SE low grille Cabriolet.
That's right, I said, "low grille."
They only made this low-profile
hood line and front grille in 1970.
It's rare. There's only about 200 of them.
This delicious car is finished
in tobacco brown
with a beige leather interior,
a 2.8 liter, six-cylinder
that's just old-school Mercedes solid.
This is a car that says,
"However I did it, I got some money.
I earned it, I stole it, I married it,
whatever. I got it.
I'm financially comfortable.
I want to be physically comfortable."
[phone rings]
-[Ali] Hello?
-[Jerry] Ali?
-[Ali] Jerry?
-I'm almost at your house.
[Ali] I'm excited. Get me out of here.
[Jerry] My guest this week
is the hilarious Ali Wentworth.
Who is not only talented and funny,
but she's also married
to George Stephanopoulos.
And Ali and George
happen to be very close friends
of Mrs. Seinfeld and myself.
Ali's one of the only WASPy people I know,
so I got this WASPy car.
This is gonna be easy.
I'm Jerry Seinfeld, and it's WASPy week
on Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee.
[horn honks]
-[Jerry] I love your hair like this.
-Thank you.
[camera shutter clicks]
-Here's the car.
-Oh, my God.
I love this car. My God, it's my people.
Look at this white steering wheel, Ali.
-Is that chic, or what?
-So chic.
How right do you look and feel right now?
-[Ali] You wanna be a WASP today?
-Yes.
Everybody always says, "Oh, WASP."
"Oh, my gosh, your ancestor
was captain of the Mayflower."
But everyone on the Mayflower,
they were all just pimps and thieves.
My mother's name is Muffie.
And you can't grow up
with a mother named Muffie
and then not mock it.
[Jerry] Do you think I could work
at all in that culture?
[Ali] You have a little bit of
an aloof facade that works very well,
because there's no emotions.
And all our genitals are spackled shut,
so there's no that.
[Jerry] Do you think
I could be married to a WASP?
[Ali] I don't think you'd like it.
If you equate it, even on a sexual level,
she's redoing her closet during sex.
And you know it, but you're...
It's a transaction.
Everyone just wants to get to sleep.
[Jerry] Who gets the credit for going,
"Hey, these people
are kind of fun to be like"?
-Ralph Lauren, first.
-Ralph.
And he sold the lifestyle, which...
My people thank him for that.
And there he is.
We're talking about Ralph Lauren
right in front of his store!
Look at that cute, little,
fuzzy brown dog.
Don't you want to just take him
and put him in some soapy water
-and wash something?
-Yeah.
Oh, the bus decided he was gonna go.
Just imagine being a bus driver
in this city. Forget it.
-You'll do what you need to do.
-Do what you need to do.
-Get those people to work... Yeah.
-You work around me.
They probably saw Speed
and thought it was a documentary.
I have a lot of friends,
and George just...
I can't deal with the husband
or I can't deal with the wife.
For two couples to hang out,
four relationships
have to function on some level.
-That's exactly right.
-Four.
If it's not four out of four,
it doesn't work.
Do you know...
when George and I are walking alone,
what do you think
he and I are talking about?
-"How do we get out of this?"
-[laughs]
[Jerry] Our kids go to the same school.
Were you there on orientation night?
The truth is, we left early.
[Jerry] I was literally biting my tongue
when they started in with,
"You know,
sixth grade is a big adjustment."
I just wanna go, "Really? Really?
Who cares?
How about they just adjust to it then
and we not worry about it?
And why don't you handle it?"
"We're not doing this together.
This is your job."
-"Yeah, you do it."
-"We feed them at the end of the day.
That's what we do."
Let's make sure their environment
is so perfectly habitable,
they are completely unprepared
for real life.
These kids, criticize them,
and they're like, "What?
What are you talking about?
So far,
everyone's loved everything I've done."
[Jerry] That's a funny sight.
Those two vehicles side-by-side?
Who loses this collision?
[Jerry] Do you wanna put the top up?
If I were smart,
I would've brought an Hermès scarf,
-so my hair wouldn't...
-Do you wanna buy one?
Let's head up Madison,
and we're gonna find a silk scarf.
-Blue Tree, right here.
-Okay.
[Ali] I'm looking for a silk scarf.
If my mother taught me anything...
[Jerry] Women in the mirror kill me.
I know, but at least I'm not going...
-I go, "What's that?"
-You can't hold that face all day.
No.
This is the WASPy-girl thing to do.
You take your bag and you go...
Oh, no. Now we've littered.
But we're WASPs, we don't care.
-[Ali] I'm gonna figure this out. Yep.
-Put your scarf on.
[Jerry]
I don't think you know how to do that.
[Jerry] What a day for a drive.
[Ali] I'm gonna give you
a perfect example of WASP.
When I was in therapy in L.A.,
we talked about depression.
And I came back and I said to my parents,
"Is there a history of depression
in our family?"
And both my mother and father said, "No!"
And I said to my mother,
"Didn't my grandparents kill themselves?"
But in their minds,
"No, they just died of natural causes."
-That's WASPy.
-Well, yeah.
All causes are natural.
[Ali] One of my favorite things
my mom ever said was,
I had just given birth to Elliott.
You're in labor, you're sweating.
It's a horrible, messy ordeal.
And my mother came in and said,
"It wouldn't hurt you to put a little
lip gloss on before George comes in."
And it sticks with you a little bit.
[Jerry] Oh, this looks fancy.
What do I do with the car?
[Ali] You could leave it running,
but you also can toss the keys.
[Jerry] I wanna do that.
I've never tossed a set of keys.
-[Ali] Thank you.
-[man] You're welcome.
-That's the way you do it.
-[Ali] Now you're gettin' it.
[classical music playing]
Oh! He'll pay for that.
-I heard a good line recently.
-Yeah?
What is a trick to a long marriage?
Don't get divorced.
-That's a little dumb.
-What do you mean?
Nobody just wants a long marriage.
-It's like having a long leg.
-But I like the simplicity of it.
Yeah, it's simple because
it's devoid of thought.
As you know,
there's nothing more that I love
than another couple having problems.
Yes. I think of it as battle
because you know how to kill.
You know the weapons they have,
you know their hideaway.
Like, if you know all that stuff...
I want to know what we're talking about.
It has to be specific. What is the fight?
-I'm gonna give you the latest fight.
-Okay.
All right, so, I've hurt my leg.
I mean, I am bandaged up,
up on pillows, and I can't walk.
-What, did you just scrape it on a rock?
-Falling into the rocks.
But I'm telling you,
it was down and it opened
and you could carve your initials
on my bone.
There was the bone.
And by the way, if I showed you
a photograph of the wound,
which he was sent from the hospital,
you would vomit in your mouth.
I'm back from Iraq, that's how bad it was.
So, the first thing George said to me
after I called him,
after I've come out of the operating room
where I was under general anesthesia, was,
"You better rest up.
You have a lot of unpacking to do."
All right, I'm gonna take a Percocet
and let that one go.
If there's another one,
I'm gonna grenade up.
But right now, I'm just gonna let that go.
So, we go back to the city
in silence in the car...
-You're in the fight now.
-Yeah.
We're not screaming, it's silence.
And that's a bad one.
If you shift or anything
in the car, it just...
It echoes like a smashed glass on slate.
The drive felt like two days, you know.
Just... with seething.
Now, what is he upset about?
That's what I can't figure out.
When people tell you a story
of some horrible incident,
the way they portray themself in the story
is unbelievably reasonable.
So, I'm beating a homeless man
with a golf club.
Not because I'm angry,
but just because he didn't belong there.
-Right. Yeah.
-Their side of it is always so reasonable.
We have talked about the style
in which we fight, which has changed.
-You're not allowed to get ghetto...
-You and George would get ghetto?
I'm speaking for myself.
Here's what I learned,
the more I really do listen to him,
without just going,
"Go ahead. What's your thing?"
[mutters]
I really listen to him,
I realized he's just going,
"How is our world gonna work
if Ali's not up..."
Now, what do I have to do
to ensure that when I'm down,
I have adequate backup?
This is all, like, cop, drug unit talk,
by the way.
-"I'm down. Backup."
-Yeah.
Do you have, like, a walkie in your house?
Why do wives always, at some point,
have to ask their husbands,
"What would you do if I died?"
Um...
It's totally narcissistic.
They want to think
that they're irreplaceable.
If you really answered and said,
"If you died, I'd probably mourn
and then I would marry
a nice 34-year-old."
-No.
No.
My husband, I would say,
would not remarry.
I know, but if he says to you that,
would you believe it?
-Yes.
-Would you care if he's lying?
No, because how will I know? I'm dead.
That isn't really answering my question.
-Would you care if he's lying?
-No, because that's what I wanna hear.
Yeah. George's father
said something really interesting to me.
I was talking about my leg and I said,
"Thank God it didn't get an infection,"
'cause, you know,
"George, I don't think
would want a one-legged wife."
Remember, he's a priest. And he looked
at me very seriously and he said,
"No. I raised my son
to be a one-wife man."
And I went, "Oh, I'm just kidding."
Well, first, it's always astounding
how humorless people can be.
Secondly, how do you raise
someone that way?
I have an 11-year-old and nine-year-old.
Should I start?
By the way, when you're done
with that LEGO Star Wars,
I wanna talk to you about
how many wives you should have.
Let me tell you the bottom line, okay?
-You want the bottom line?
-Yeah, give me the bottom line.
Men don't talk to each other.
They don't have another guy say to them,
"Does your wife do this?"
Because 99.99% of the time,
the answer's gonna be,
"Yeah, she does. Does yours?"
"Yeah, she does. How do you handle it?"
"How do you handle it?"
They don't do any of this.
Just that is going to improve
all these marriages, 90%.
-Here's the level I'm on, okay?
-That seems higher than my level.
It is. I have absolutely no interest
in being right.
I used to have feelings.
Those feelings got in my way.
I got rid of those feelings.
But you would drive me crazy
if I were married to you.
Why aren't you sticking up
for the fact that you're right?
-Give me an example, smarty-pants.
-All right. Okay.
Give me an example
where I'm right and you're wrong,
and you need to be shown
that you're wrong.
And, by the way, take your time.
[gentle music playing]
So, next week, I'm gonna go...
Why's that funny?
You're acting like
we're in the kitchen, eating.
Because when you're not sure
how it's gonna be taken,
you look down, you have to busy yourself.
So, next week, me and some girlfriends
-are gonna go to a spa.
-That sounds nice.
But I'm gonna need you
to be all over the kids.
Lenny has cello, Persephone has ballet,
and Cassiopeia...
Were you looking
in a telescope last night?
But you're too happy about that.
-You're never...
-You're going to the spa...
-You're not giving me any conflict.
-Why should I?
-You don't deserve any.
-I need something to get me...
Well, then come up with a better premise.
All right.
I've met someone...
[both laugh]
-[Jerry] Thank you.
-[Ali] Thank you.
[Ali] Now, when you take these cars out,
is there an option to buy?
-Are these cars for sale?
-Everything's for sale, honey.
-Even you.
-That I know.
-Yeah.
Do you know
there was once a well-known writer
who offered me $40,000.
I would keep that in my back pocket
in your next fight with George.
-"I'll have you know..."
-"Forty." "Forty?"
-It's an odd number, by the way.
-Yeah.
Fifty, I could see. Twenty, I could see.
Forty is like
he thought about it a little.
"She's worth 50. Maybe I can get 10 off."
Here's what I don't understand.
The guys, that years later,
you find out that he had a whole family
in a different state.
-Charles Lindbergh and Charles Kuralt.
-Exhausting.
And who are the wives
that haven't figured that out?
Come on. Women are like pigs to truffles.
Where were you that three-day weekend?
We didn't see you.
You didn't call, you didn't...
[Jerry] I pitched my wife Mormonism.
Here's the genius of polygamy.
Most women do not want
a man around that much.
-Yeah.
-Once a week, twice a week.
-Plenty.
-Yeah.
Most men would like to be
with different women.
-Yeah.
-If you can afford it,
where's the victim?
[Ali] Well, in Mormonism,
they all live together.
-[Jerry] Yeah.
-That's too many people for me.
-Right, I agree with that.
-I don't... No, that's too much.
I think the real loser
in that scenario is the man.
Because men think they want more women.
You don't want more women.
One woman is plenty.
[Ali] We're at that stage where the kids
are happily ensconced in school.
We're not gonna do anything wild.
We're not adopting a Korean boy.
-We're not gonna mix it up too much.
-Right.
The little Korean boy,
right now watching this,
a tear just rolled down his face.
Right.
[Jerry] I remember George telling me
one of the greatest husband lines
I've ever heard,
and I'm gonna do it for you now.
Okay.
[Jerry] We were talking about how
you guys moved up here from D.C.,
and you're living
in a New York apartment now.
Are you happy here?
He goes, "Geez, I sure hope we are."
[both laugh]
[Jerry] The point being, he has no idea.
-He'll be informed if he's happy.
-[Ali] Yes, exactly. Yes.
[Ali] Do you know, when I first met you,
you were trying to remember the joke
about the lemon meringue pie.
-[Jerry] No, it's Bavarian cream pie.
-That's what it was!
-[Jerry] Bavarian cream pie.
-Yep.
Here's the joke. So, there's a man.
He's a soldier in World War II.
He stops into a little German bakery,
has a piece of Bavarian cream pie.
It's the greatest thing he's ever had.
The war ends, he goes home,
he gets married, raises a family,
the kids go to college,
the wife eventually passes away,
he goes to the doctor, the doctor says,
"You have six months to live."
He's done everything
he wanted to do in life.
There's only one thing
that he would like to experience again,
and that is to have another piece
of that Bavarian cream pie.
And so, he books passage
on an ocean liner.
Halfway across the Atlantic,
the ocean liner hits an iceberg and sinks.
The life raft runs out of air
and he falls into the water.
Now he starts to swim,
but he's getting eaten by sharks.
His legs and arms are both completely
eaten off and he's lost a lot of blood.
But he lands on the coast of France,
and he begins to crawl.
He crawls across France,
across Switzerland,
finds his way into Germany,
asking directions.
He crawls into the bakery,
pulls himself onto an empty stool.
No arms, no legs,
cancer riddled through his body and brain.
The waitress says,
"May I take your order?"
He says, "I would like a piece
of Bavarian cream pie."
The waitress says, "Oh, gee.
I'm sorry. I just sold our last piece."
-Yeah?
-He goes, "I'll have peach."
[Ali] I think it's funnier if she said,
"I just sold the last piece."
Then he should go,
"I'll just have a cup of coffee."
[laughing]
I think it's better!
-It is. You're right.
-Yeah!